Office of the Vice-President, University Services fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- University Services Departments, 1970 - 1977; F-207-4; 64 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the operation and daily administration of University Services Departments on campus and includes Vice-President's correspondence with university services departments, members of the university community, and external organizations; planning documents; staff memoranda; annual reports; and project proposals. Records include correspondence, working papers and reports, agendas and minutes, budgets and financial statements, annual reports, statistics, surveys, contracts, newspaper clippings and publications.
  - Counselling Services, 1970 - 1977; F-207-4-1; 6 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the daily administration of Counselling Services and the Vice-President's correspondence with Counselling personnel and the university community; development of counselling progams, service policies and procedures regarding the disclosure of student information; and budget and space planning. Records include correspondence and working papers, annual reports, financial statements, statistics, and publications.
    - Information pamphlets, [197-?]; F-207-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-6)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-16.
    - Reports, 1971; F-207-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-6)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-2.
    - General, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-6)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-5.
    - Correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-12.
    - Space, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-6.
    - Utilization of University Counselling Service, 1972 - 1973; F-207-4-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-7.
    - Annual Report, 1973; F-207-4-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-6-0-5.
    - Correspondence, 1973; F-207-4-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-13.
    - Annual Report, 1974; F-207-4-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-6-0-6.
    - Disclosure of Information, 1974; F-207-4-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-8.
    - Correspondence, 1974 - 1977; F-207-4-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-1-14.
    - Annual Report, 1975; F-207-4-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-6-0-7.
    - Annual Report, 1976; F-207-4-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-6-0-8.
    - Annual Report, 1977; F-207-4-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-6-0-9.
  - Health Services, 1971 - 1977; F-207-4-2; 8 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the daily administration of Health Services and the Vice-President's correspondence with Health Services personnel, the university community, and the British Columbia Medical Services Commission; policy development and budget planning, space shortages and proposals for expansion of the department, the report "University Health Needs" and reports on the history of Health Services, implementation of student medical insurance, and papers of the Health Advisory Committee. Records include correspondence, working papers and reports, agendas and minutes, annual reports, statistics, and financial statements.
    British Columbia Medical Services Commission
    - Report on University Health Needs, 1971; F-207-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-28.
    - Space, 1971; F-207-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-24.
    - Health Services - General, 1971; F-207-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-9.
    - B.C. Medical Services Commission, 1971; F-207-4-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-15.
    - Policy, 1971; F-207-4-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-19.
    - Personnel, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-26.
    - Proposals, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-21.
    - Medical Insurance, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-18.
    - Budget, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-16.
    - Health Services - General, 1972; F-207-4-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-10.
    - Administration and Organization, 1972; F-207-4-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-14.
    - Reports and Statistics, 1972; F-207-4-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-23.
    - History of Health Services, 1972; F-207-4-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-1.
    - Annual Reports, 1972 - 1974; F-207-4-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-20.
    - Correspondence, 1973; F-207-4-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-2.
    - Health Advisory Committee, 1973 - 1974; F-207-4-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-7.
    - Correspondence, 1974; F-207-4-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-3.
    - Inventory of Moveable Equipment, 1975; F-207-4-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-4.
    - Correspondence, 1975; F-207-4-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-5.
    - Physical Expansion, 1975; F-207-4-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-6.
    - Correspondence, 1977; F-207-4-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 207-7)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-2-8.
  - Reading and Study Centre, 1971 - 1976; F-207-4-3; 3 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the daily administration of the Reading and Study Centre and includes Vice-President's correspondence with Centre personnel; job descriptions and resumes; proposed budget and fees; syllabus development and literacy tests; and program status reports produced each semester. Records include correspondence, working papers and reports, statistics, annual reports, financial statements, and publications.
    - General, 1971; F-207-4-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-3-5.
    - Reports, vol. 1, 1971 - 1975; F-207-4-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-3-2.
    - Reports, vol. 2, 1971 - 1975; F-207-4-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-3-1.
    - External Review, 1975 - 1976; F-207-4-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-3-7.
  - Housing and Residences, 1970 - 1977; F-207-4-4; 24 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the daily administration of housing and residences on campus and the Vice-President's correspondence with Housing and Residence staff, the Board of Governors, and members of the university community regarding children's play areas, food services, family residences, conference accommodations, and living conditions; development of rent collection policies and residence rules; new housing proposals; student rental inquiries; and budget and operating statements. Also included are records of the Residence Planning and Policy Committee and the Residences Tenants' Association and student housing questionnaires. Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas and minutes, reports, financial statements, surveys, statistics, contracts, and publications.
    Food Services; Board of Governors
    - Rent Collection Policy, 1970 - 1971; F-207-4-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-63.
    - Overdue Accounts, 1970 - 1971; F-207-4-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-42.
    - Indoor Play Area, 1971; F-207-4-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-41.
    - Residence Planning and Policy Committee, 1971; F-207-4-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-43.
    - Shell House, 1971; F-207-4-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-48.
    - CAUBO - Residences and Food Service Survey, 1971; F-207-4-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-50.
    - Reports and Statistics, 1971; F-207-4-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-51.
    - General, 1971; F-207-4-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-59.
    - Enquiries, 1971; F-207-4-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-32.
    - Budget, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-28.
    - Food Service, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-33.
    - Family Residences, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-49.
    - Apartments, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-47.
    - Conference Accommodation, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-46.
    - Policies, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-44.
    - Student Housing Questionnaire, 1972; F-207-4-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 207-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-23.
    - General, 1972; F-207-4-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-8.
    - Simon Fraser Student Housing Survey, 1972; F-207-4-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-6.
    - General, vol. 1, 1973; F-207-4-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-3.
    - General, vol. 2, 1973; F-207-4-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-10.
    - Budget, 1973; F-207-4-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-4.
    - Housing Proposal, 1973; F-207-4-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-5.
    - Children's Activity Centre, 1973 - 1974; F-207-4-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-14.
    - General, 1974; F-207-4-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-13.
    - New Housing Proposal, 1974; F-207-4-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-15.
    - Other Universities re: Residences, 1974; F-207-4-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-16.
    - Proposed Student Residences, 1974; F-207-4-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-24.
    - Central Mortgage and Housing, 1974; F-207-4-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-17.
    - Board of Governors re: Housing, 1974; F-207-4-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-18.
    - General, 1975; F-207-4-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-19.
    - Operating Statements, 1975; F-207-4-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-20.
    - Residential Village at S.F.U., 1975; F-207-4-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 207-9)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-22.
    - Summer Student Housing Questionnaire, 1975; F-207-4-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-7.
    - Residences Tenants' Association, 1975; F-207-4-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Restricted in part
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-21.
    - General, 1976 - 1977; F-207-4-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-26.1.
    - New Residences, 1977; F-207-4-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-4-26.2.
  - International Office, 1973 - 1975; F-207-4-5; 2 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the daily administration of the International Office on campus and the Vice-President's correspondence with staff regarding personnel issues and the development of goals, objectives, and policies; budget and grant proposals; planning activities for foreign students; correspondence with the Canadian Bureau for International Education (CBIE) and World University Service of Canada (WUSC), and minutes of Canadian University Students Overseas (CUSO) meetings; foreign student statistics; and International Office brochures. Also included are reports on the role of the International Office at SFU, the Study Abroad Program for SFU students, and "International Education at SFU" by the International Office Task Force. Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas and minutes, reports, financial statements, statistics, and publications.
    Canadian Bureau for International Education; World University Service
    - General, 1973; F-207-4-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-5-3.
    - International Office Task Force, vol. 1, 1975; F-207-4-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-5-1.
    - International Office Task Force, vol. 2, 1975; F-207-4-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-5-2.
  - Centre for Communications and the Arts, 1970 - 1975; F-207-4-6; 9 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the daily administration of the Centre for Communications and the Arts and the Vice-President's correspondence with staff and the university community regarding music, films and theatre projects and exhibitions; minutes of Arts Centre staff meetings; budget development and grant applications; non-credit workshop planning and facility management. Also included are correspondence with the Advisory Committee on the Arts; a report on campus communications; and planning and promotional materials for the premier of the movie "Groundstar Conspiracy" that was filmed at SFU. Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas and minutes, reports, financial statements, contracts, newspaper clippings, and publications.
    - Music - General, 1970; F-207-4-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-9.
    - Music - Sonic Research Studio, 1970; F-207-4-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-11.
    - General, 1970 - 1971; F-207-4-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-1.
    - Arts Centre Meetings, 1970 - 1971; F-207-4-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-8.
    - Residents - Contracts, 1970 - 1971; F-207-4-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-12.
    - Film, 1970 - 1972; F-207-4-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Open, no restrictions
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-6.
      Access review (May 30, 2023) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Budget, 1970 - 1972; F-207-4-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-3.
    - Advisory Committee on the Arts, 1971; F-207-4-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-2.
    - Theatre, 1971; F-207-4-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-13.
    - Grant Applications, 1971; F-207-4-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-7.
    - Curator Exhibitions, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-5.
    - Facilities, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-15.
    - Non-credit Workshops, 1971 - 1972; F-207-4-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-10.
    - Movie - "Groundstar Conspiracy", 1972; F-207-4-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-14.
    - General, 1972; F-207-4-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-16.
    - Report on Campus Communications, 1973; F-207-4-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-17.
    - General, 1975; F-207-4-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-18.
    - Budget, 1975; F-207-4-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 207-10)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-1-4-6-4.
  - Daycare Centre, 1971 - 1977; F-207-4-7; 13 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records relating to the daily administration of the Daycare Centre and the Vice-President's correspondence with staff and the university community regarding personnel issues, polices and procedures, construction of the Daycare Centre, and operation of Nanitsh, Kahpoo, and Pink daycare centres; budgets, funding proposals and cashbooks; daycare incorporation documents; minutes of the Burnaby Mountain Day Care Society; and reports on the history of daycare on campus. Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas and minutes, reports, financial statements, and publications.
    Nanitsh Daycare Society; Kahpoo Daycare Society; Pink Daycare Society; Simon Fraser University Childcare Society
    - Correspondence, 1971 - 1974; F-207-4-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-2.
    - Construction Correspondence, 1972 - 1977; F-207-4-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-9.
    - SFU and Burnaby Mt. - Legal Documents, 1973; F-207-4-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-23.
    - Personnel and Operations, 1973 - 1974; F-207-4-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-20.
    - Burnaby Mt. Day Care Society Minutes, 1973 - 1974; F-207-4-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-25.
    - Cashbooks, 1973 - 1974; F-207-4-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-19.
    - Budgets and Accounts, 1973 - 1977; F-207-4-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-15.
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-4-0-1.
    - Day Care Study, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-10.
    - Nanitsh Day Care Society, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-5-0-1.
    - Kahpoo Day Care Society, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-2-0-1.
    - Pink Day Care Society, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-3-0-1.
    - General, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-4-0-2.
    - Correspondence, vol. 1, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-3.
    - Correspondence, vol. 2, 1974; F-207-4-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-4.
    - Correspondence, 1975; F-207-4-7-0-16 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-6.
    - Correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-207-4-7-0-17 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-5.
    - Budget Proposals, 1977; F-207-4-7-0-18 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-16.
    - History of Daycare on Campus, 1977; F-207-4-7-0-19 (Archival box - standard 207-11)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-54-5-1-0-1.
- Assistant to Vice-President, University Services, 1971 - 1975; F-207-5; 37 cm of textual records